lifecare.com 2011-05-31

# Privacy Policy : LifeCare

THE POLICY  
This privacy policy will advise you about how we protect your personal information. Please read this policy carefully. This policy applies to your use of all of the sites and services owned or operated by LifeCare and any other site that we may own or operate currently or in the future (collectively, the "LifeCare Sites"). Unless we say otherwise, all references to the LifeCare Sites in this policy include all such sites. This policy does not apply to any sites other than the LifeCare Sites. 

We may need to change this policy from time to time, so you should refer back to this policy regularly. Your use of the system after changes have been made shall be deemed to be your acceptance of any changes. If you do not accept any changes that are made to this policy, do not use this site. 

Protecting your privacy and your information is a top priority. We have taken careful measures to secure your information. Our secure server software encrypts information, ensuring that all Internet transactions from your PC to our servers remain private (unless sent by an unsecured means, such as e-mail). Use of this encryption is facilitated automatically. To protect the integrity and confidentiality of your personal information, our web servers reside behind firewalls. In addition to these security measures, only our employees who need access to your personal information to carry out their duties have access to that information. Our employees must abide by our company's privacy policy, and are subject to disciplinary action for any violation of that policy.

The confidentiality of any information you submit is protected by the Privacy Act of 1974, 5 U.S.C. 552a, and its implementing regulations, including 45 C.F.R. Part 5b; see also 67 Fed. Reg. 4965 (2002) (Employee Assistance Program System of Records Notice) to the extent applicable. Information collected from Federal employees is covered under the Privacy Act of 1974.

THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
This policy applies to all information collected about you as an individual user through the LifeCare sites.

When you browse through our web site, certain information about you can be collected. We automatically collect the following information about your visit: the name of the domain you used to access the web site, the date and time of your visit, the pages you visited and the address of the web site that referred you to our web site. We use this information for statistical purposes and to help us make our site more useful to visitors.

We only collect personally identifiable information about you that is necessary for us to allow you to utilize our services, and only to the extent specifically provided in this policy and/or allowed by applicable law. By using the LifeCare Sites, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information in the manner provided in this policy.

DISCLOSURE OF USER PERSONAL INFORMATION   
We will not disclose personal or proprietary information, which we obtain in the course of providing services to you, to any third party except: (1) as required by law, or (2) consistent with applicable law, and as follows:

  * We may disclose personal information to a service provider to perform a specific service on our behalf, but only when consistent with this policy and subject to a contract that:

    1. Prohibits them from using the information for any other purpose;
    2. requires them to conform to our privacy and security obligations; and
    3. allows for an audit of their compliance.

  * We will not share your personal information to any third party except as set forth above and, except at your direction or as part of de-identified aggregated reports.

In addition, we will release specific information about you to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute or court order. We will also release specific information in special cases, such as if there is an attempted breach of the security of the LifeCare Sites, or a physical threat to you or others, or to report to law enforcement officials any activities that we reasonably believe to be unlawful where we reasonably believe that you are, have been, or may in the future be engaged or otherwise involved in such activities. While LifeCare maintains a secure site, you should know that computer use may be monitored by third parties such as network administrators, employers, etc., and thus we can not guarantee the security of information you post online. You disclose such information at your own risk.

PRIVACY OF CHILDREN   
LifeCare realizes that children under the age of 13 may not understand all the provisions of our policy or be able to make thoughtful decisions about the choices made available. We urge all parents to participate in their children's exploration of the Internet and any online services, and to teach their children about protecting their personal information while online. Therefore, LifeCare will not allow users under the age of 13 to use the site without the consent of their parent or guardian. 

THIRD PARTY CONTENT PROVIDERS/LINKS   
Users will find contents and products of other companies or organizations on our sites and/or links to the sites and services of our suppliers, licensors or other third parties. While we make efforts to monitor the sites or services, we do not control the contents or links that appear on these sites. Each such third party is solely responsible for complying with the laws, rules and regulations applicable to its business, operation of its web site(s), and the use of your personal information, including all applicable laws, rules and regulations regarding the privacy and confidentiality of individually identifiable health information such as the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (HIPAA) and the regulations promulgated under HIPAA. We are not responsible for the privacy practices, the content, or the legal and regulatory compliance of such sites and their owners and operators. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies, or no policy (policies) at all. These sites or services, including their contents and links, may be constantly changing. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party sites or services before providing any of them with your personal information. 

USES OF COOKIES  
LifeCare provides you with the opportunity to volunteer personal information while interacting with the many features of our site. In addition, visitor information may be collected automatically as you navigate through our sites. Personal and/or visitor information can be anything that identifies you or your accounts. These "cookies" of information may be used by us to help us manage the site and provide functionality to you, but we do not use this information for direct marketing or solicitation of business and do not provide this information to third parties except as required by law. LifeCare leverages session cookies only. These are not permanent cookies and are removed from when your browser closes or your computer is powered off.

CORRECTING AND REMOVING YOUR INFORMATION  
f you would like to correct any personal information you have provided to us or request that we remove your information from our records, e-mail us at [help@lifecare.com](mailto:help@lifecare.com "Click here to e-mail the help desk") with the correction or a request for a more secure way to communicate with us.

INTRUSION DETECTION   
For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we employ software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations, and pursuant to any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help identify an individual.

ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS   
By using any of the LifeCare Sites, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. Your continued use of the LifeCare Sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.

Last Updated: September 2009

Copyright © 2009, LifeCare®, Inc. 2 Armstrong Road, Shelton, CT 06484, (203) 226-2680. All rights reserved.
